OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/020
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Public agreements: Code nos.810064-810302 (Box 64)
  - 810108, 1995-1997 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    1/1/1995 - 1/1/1997
  - 810108, 2001-2002 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    January 1 2001 - December 31 2002
  - 810132, 2001-2005 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    7/1/2001 - 6/30/2005
  - 810164, 2003-2004 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    July 1 2003 - June 30 2004
  - 810137, 2003-2006 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - 810162, 2000-2002 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - 810165, 2003-2004 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - 810166, 2002-2006 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - 810179, 2002-2004 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - 810181, 2002-2005 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - 810182, 2001-2004 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - 810183, 2003-2005 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    June 3 2003 - 2005
  - 810184, 2003-2005 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - 810185, 2003-2005 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - 810190, 2002-2005 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - 810191, 2002-2004 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - 810192, 2002-2003 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - 810193, 1997-1998 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    7/1/1997 - 6/30/1998
  - 810302, 2001-2003 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    January 1 2001 - December 31 2003
  - Folder List Index Box # 64 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Public agreements: Code nos.81750-811635 (Box 65)
  - 811213, 2003-2005 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - 810750, 2004-2005 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - 811248, 2002-2006 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    City of Trenton
  - 811250, 2000-2003 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - 811251, 1997-2005 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    University of Connecticut Board of Trustee
  - 811265, 1996-2004 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - 811276, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    Memphis Light Gas and Water Division
  - 811280, 2001-2004 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    State of Florida
  - 811284, 2003-2005 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    City of St. Petersburg
  - 811288, 2001-2004 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    Town of Hempstead
  - 811290, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    Stockton Unified School District
  - 811292, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - 811294, 1999-2006 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    County of Santa Clara
  - 811055, 2002-2003 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - 811116, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    DC Department of Corrections
  - 811146, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    City of Dayton, Ohio
  - 811152, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - 811191, 2002-2006 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    City of Las Vegas, Nevada
  - 811202, 1998-2001 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - 811212, 2003-2004 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - 811213, 2003-2005 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    Board of Regents, State of Iowa
  - 811214, 2001-2006 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    Jefferson County Fiscal Court
  - 811215, 2001-2004 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    School Board of Polk County, Florida
  - 811314, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - 811320, 2001-2005 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - 811321, 2001-2005 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - 811322, 1997-1999 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    State of Oregon Department of Administration Service
  - 811324, 2001-2003 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    Portland Federation of Teachers and Employee
  - 811325, 2003-2006 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    Federal Way School District
  - 811331, 2000-2003 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    City of Albuquerque
  - 811425, 2001-2005 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    City of Glendale
  - 811431, 2000-2002 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - 811432, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    Commissioner Labor Relation and Health and Hospital Corporation
  - 811433, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    Commissioner of Labor Relation, City of New York
  - 811434, 2000-2002 (Box 65, Folder 35)
    Commissioner of Labor Relation
  - 811435, 2001-2002 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - 811470, 1999-2002 (Box 65, Folder 37)
    New York Transit Authority
  - 811471, 2003-2006 (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - 811472, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 39)
    Commissioner of Labor Relation Health and Hospital
  - 811475, 2000-2002 (Box 65, Folder 40)
    NY School Construction Authority
  - 811484, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 41)
    City of Columbus
  - 811490, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 42)
    City of Tampa
  - 811551, 2003-2004 (Box 65, Folder 43)
    City of Wichita, Kansas
  - 811620, 2002-2005 (Box 65, Folder 44)
    School Board of Hillsborough County
  - Folder List Index Box # 65 (Box 65, Folder 45)
- Public agreements: Code nos.800357-800404 (Box 66)
  - 800357, 2001-2006 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    July 2 2001 - June 30 2006; CDF Firefighters
  - 800359, 2002-2004 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    1/1/2002 - 12/31/2004; State of Michigan
  - 800360, 2003-2005 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    State of Vermont
  - 800361, 2001-2003 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    July 1 2001 - July 2 2003; State of California
  - 800362, 2003-2006 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    July 1 2003 - July 1 2006; State of California
  - 800363, 2001-2006 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    July 3 2001 - July 2 2006; State of California
  - 800364, 2001-2003 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    July 1 2001 - June 30 2003; State of California
  - 800366, 2002-2005 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    January 1 2002 - September 30 2005; State of Michigan
  - 800367, 1993-1995 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    July 1 1993 - June 30 1995; State of Iowa
  - 800368, 2001-2006 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    July 1 2001 - July 2 2006; State of California
  - 800369, 2003-2005 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    July 3 2003 - June 30 2005; State of California
  - 800370, 2003-2005 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - 800371, 2003-2005 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    July 1 2003 - June 30 2005; State of Nebraska
  - 800372, 2003-2005 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - 800374, 1994-1997 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    January 1 1994 - June 30 1997; State of Indiana
  - 800379, 2003-2005 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    July 1 2003 - June 30 2005; University of Minnesota
  - 800380, 2001-2004 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    July 1 2001 - June 30 2004; Medical College of Ohio
  - 800382, 2002-2006 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    July 1 2002 - June 30 2006; State of Connecticut
  - 800383, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    6/1994
  - 800389, 2002-2003 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    7/1/2002 - June 30 2003; State of Wisconsin
  - 800391, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    6/30/2004
  - 800392, 2002-2006 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - 800393, 2000-2003 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    State of Ohio
  - 800395, 2001-2005 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    July 1 2001 - June 30 2005; State of Connecticut
  - 800397, 2000-2003 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - 800402, 1999-2003 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    4/2/1999 - 3/31/2003; New York State
  - 800403, 1999-2003 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    State of New York
  - 800404, 1988-1991 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Folder List Index Box # 66 (Box 66, Folder 29)
- Public agreements: Code nos.830651-830754 (Box 67)
  - 830651, 2003-2004 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    Dayton City School District
  - 830668, 1989-1992 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Brentwood NY Union Free School District
  - 830677, 1998-2004 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Jefferson County Board of Education
  - 830684, 1999-2002 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Board of Education of School District City of Detroit
  - 830688, 2001-2006 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - 830695, 2002-2003 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - 830697, 2002-2006 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    University of Connecticut Board of Trustees
  - 830703, 2003-2006 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    Board of Education Memphis City Schools
  - 830705, 2003-2005 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    South Bend Community School
  - 830706, 2003-2005 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    School Board of Independent School District 281
  - 830707, 2001-2004 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Board of Education Frederick County
  - 830708, 2002-2005 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    Toms River Board of Education
  - 830709, 2003-2006 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    Board of Education Prince George County, Maryland
  - 830710, 2004-2006 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    Board of Education School District Colorado Springs
  - 830712, 1999-2002 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    School District of Palm Beach County
  - 830713, 2001-2005 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - 830714, 2000-2002 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    Board of Education Anne Arundel County
  - 830715, 2002-2005 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - 830716, 1992-1993 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    Anne Arundel County
  - 830717, 2002-2004 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    Jefferson County KY Board of Education
  - 830718, 2003-2006 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    Sarasota County School Board
  - 830719, 2000-2002 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    City University of NY Classified Service
  - 830720, 2003-2006 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    School Board of Sarasota County
  - 830721, 2001-2003 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    Milwaukee Public School Directors
  - 830722, 2001-2003 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    Evansville-Vanderburgh School
  - 830723, 2001-2004 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    Board of Education Unified School District 512
  - 830724, 2003-2006 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    School District of Clay County
  - 830726, 2000-2002 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    Board of Education of Prince Georges County
  - 830727, 2004-2006 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - 830728, 1990-2002 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    City University of NY
  - 830730, 1999-2002 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - 830731, 1999-2003 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    Chicago School Reform Board of Trustees
  - 830732, 2000-2003 (Box 67, Folder 33)
    District of Columbia Board of Education
  - 830734, 2000-2001 (Box 67, Folder 34)
    Compton Unified School District
  - 830735, 2000-2003 (Box 67, Folder 35)
    Pinellas County Schools
  - 830736, 1999-2002 (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - 830737, 1996-2001 (Box 67, Folder 37)
    Board of Education City School District of NY
  - 830738, 1991-1994 (Box 67, Folder 38)
    Dade County Public Schools
  - 830740, 2002-2004 (Box 67, Folder 39)
    Utica Community School District
  - 830743, 2003-2005 (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - 839744, 2002-2004 (Box 67, Folder 41)
    Salem-Keiner School District 24
  - 830745, 1999-2002 (Box 67, Folder 42)
    San Jose Unified School District
  - 830746, 1999-2002 (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - 830747, 2002-2005 (Box 67, Folder 44)
    Los Angeles Community College District
  - 830749, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - 830750, 2000-2004 (Box 67, Folder 46)
    City School District Rochester, NY
  - 830751, 1995-2002 (Box 67, Folder 47)
    Board of Education of New York School District
  - 803752, 2002-2006 (Box 67, Folder 48)
  - 830754, 2002-2005 (Box 67, Folder 49)
  - Folder List Index Box # 67 (Box 67, Folder 50)
- Private agreements: Code nos.8140-8431 (Box 68)
  - 8140, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - 8142, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    January 1 2002 - December 31 2006
  - 8143, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - 8147, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - 8150, 2001-2006 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    5/31/2001 - 5/31/2006
  - 8158, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - 8160, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - 8161, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - 8163, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - 8164, 2001-2006 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - 8165, 2001-2006 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - 8166, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    6/28/2006
  - 8169, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - 8170, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - 8172, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - 8173, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - 8175, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - 8176, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - 8177, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - 8178, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - 8182, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - 8191, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - 8196, 2001-2006 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    7/1/2001 - 6/30/2006
  - 8197, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    June 1 2002 - May 31 2006
  - 8207, 2001-2006 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    March 5 2001 - March 5 2006
  - 8208, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - 8212, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - 8217, 2000-2006 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    10/12/2000 - 3/31/2006
  - 8225, 2001-2006 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    May 27 2001 - May 28 2006
  - 8233, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - 8313, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    1/1/2002 - 12/31/2006
  - 8324, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - 8329, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    June 29 2003 - June 30 2006
  - 8332, 2005-2006 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    1/31/2005 - 1/31/2006
  - 8400, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - 8401, 2002-2006 (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - 8402, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 37)
  - 8403, 2003-2005 (Box 68, Folder 38)
  - 8411, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 39)
  - 8412, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 40)
    July 17 2003 - July 16 2006
  - 8416, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 41)
  - 8417, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 42)
  - 8421, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 43)
  - 8426, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 44)
    July 21 2003 - July 16 2006
  - 8431, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 45)
    March 3 2003 March 5 2006
  - Folder List Index Box # 68 (Box 68, Folder 46)
- Public agreements: Code nos.800289-800356 (Box 69)
  - 800289, 2004-2006 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    10/18/2004 - 3/31/2006
  - 800290, 2002-2004 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - 800291, 2001-2004 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - 800292, 2002-2005 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - 800293, 2000-2004 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    July 1 2000 - June 30 2004
  - 800294, 2001-2004 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - 800295, 2003-2006 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    July 3 2003 - July 1 2006
  - 800298, 1999-2003 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    1999 - 3/31/2003
  - 800299, 1999-2003 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - 800303, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    July 1 2001 - June 30 2003
  - 800306, 1999-2003 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - 800309, 1999-2003 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - 800310, 2002-2005 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - 800311, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    10/23/2001 - 1/7/2003
  - 800315, 2003-2006 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    September 18 2003 - June 30 2006
  - 800317, 2003-2006 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - 800319, 2003-2006 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - 800320, 2002-2005 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - 800323, 2003-2005 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    10/13/2003 - 6/29/2005
  - 800325, 1999-2001 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - 800329, 2005-2006 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - 800335, 1998-2001 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    July 1 1998 - June 30 2001
  - 800336, 2003-2006 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    6/30/2003 - 6/30/2006
  - 800341, 2001-2004 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    7/1/2001 - 6/30/2004
  - 800346, 1990-1991 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - 800348, 2002-2004 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    1/1/2002 - 12/31/2004
  - 800349, 2000-2003 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - 800350, 2000-2003 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - 800352, 2003-2005 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    July 3 2003 - June 30 2005
  - 800353, 2003-2005 (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - 800354, 2003-2004 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    July 3 2003 - June 30 2004
  - 800355, 2003-2006 (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - 800356, 2002-2003 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    January 31 2002 - July 2 2003
  - Folder List Index Box # 69 (Box 69, Folder 34)
- Public agreements: Code nos.820325 (Box 70)
  - 820325, 2003-2006 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - 820345, 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    April 1 1987 - December 31 1988
  - 820344, 1996-2001 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    1996 - 12/31/2001
  - 820343, 1983-1984 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - 820341, 1980-1988 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - 820340, 1990-1992 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    January 1 1990 - December 31 1992
  - 820338, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    12/2000
  - 820328, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    9/1987
- Public agreements: Code nos.800000-800120 (Box 71)
  - 800000, 2002-2003 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    July 1 2002 - December 31 2003
  - 800004, 2003-2005 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - 800007, 2000-2004 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - 800020, 2002-2006 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    August 1 2002 - July 31 2006
  - 800033, 2003-2006 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - 800050, 2003-2006 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    July 10 2003 - June 30 2006
  - 800051, 1995-1996 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    7/8/1995 - 6/30/1996
  - 800056, 1996-1999 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    October 11 1996 - October 10 1999
  - 800064, 2002-2005 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    May 10 2002 - July 31 2005
  - 800065, 2001-2004 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    November 1 2001 - October 31 2004
  - 800069, 1977-1979 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - 800077, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    June 30 2003
  - 800099, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    July 19 2000
  - 800100, 2000-2005 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    July 1 2000 - June 30 2005
  - 800101, 2000-2002 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    July 1 2000 - September 20 2002
  - 800102, 2000-2002 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    January 1 2000 - March 31 2002
  - 800104, 2004-2006 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - 800106, 2002-2005 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - 800107, 2002-2003 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - 800108, 2003-2005 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    October 1 2003 - September 20 2005
  - 800109, 2004-2006 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - 800110, 2000-2002 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - 800111, 2001-2004 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    October 1 2001 - September 30 2004
  - 800112, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    September 2003
  - 800113, 2001-2003 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    September 1 2001 - August 31 2003
  - 800114, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    8/2005
  - 800115, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 27)
    8/2006
  - 800117, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 28)
    3 May 1996
  - 800118, 2003-2005 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - 800119, 1997-2000 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - 800120, 1999-2000 (Box 71, Folder 31)
    5/1/1999 - 4/30/2000
  - Folder List Index Box # 71 (Box 71, Folder 32)
- Private agreements: Code nos.K6718-K7413 (Box 72)
  - 6718, 2002-2006 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Stop N Shop
  - 6726, 2000-2004 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co.
  - 6745, 2002-2005 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Jewell Food Stores
  - 6746, 1999-2003 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - 6747, 2000-2004 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - 6748, 2000-2005 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - 6749, 1997-2002 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Dollars KMA
  - 6751, 1998-2003 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - 6752, 2001-2003 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - 6755, 2001-2004 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    Safeway, Altertsons, Ralphs
  - 6759, 2002-2005 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    St Paul Grocery
  - 6761, 2001-2004 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - 6764, 2000-2005 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    Meijer, Inc.
  - 6775, 2002-2006 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    Shop Rite
  - 6779, 1999-2004 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - 6780, 2000-2004 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    Kroger's
  - 6784, 2000-2002 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    Acme Markets
  - 6805, 2000-2004 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    Giant Food
  - 6819, 1999-2004 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - 6821, 2001-2004 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - 6836, 2002-2006 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    Waldbaums and Nambor Red Apple
  - 6843, 2002-2006 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - 6855, 1999-2003 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    Penn Traffic, Inc.
  - 6857, 2001-2004 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - 6860, 1999-2002 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - 6869, 2003-2005 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    Bruno's Food World
  - 6870, 2003-2004 (Box 72, Folder 27)
    Bruno's Food and Pharmacy
  - 6870, 2004-2005 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - 6871, 2000-2004 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - 6872, 1999-2004 (Box 72, Folder 30)
    King Soopers
  - 6875, 2000-2004 (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - 6883, 1999-2004 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - 6884, 1996-2004 (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - 6886, 1999-2004 (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - 6888, 2001-2005 (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - 6894, 2001-2006 (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - 6895, 2002-2006 (Box 72, Folder 37)
    Pathmark
  - 6896, 1999-2003 (Box 72, Folder 38)
    Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company
  - 6897, 2002-2005 (Box 72, Folder 39)
    Akron/Canton Food Industry
  - 6900, 2001-2006 (Box 72, Folder 40)
    Mechanical Contractors
  - 6917, 2003-2006 (Box 72, Folder 41)
    Minneapolis Auto Dealers
  - 6920, 2001-2005 (Box 72, Folder 42)
    New Car Dealer Committee
  - 6921, 2002-2006 (Box 72, Folder 43)
    Garage Attendants
  - 6925, 2001-2005 (Box 72, Folder 44)
  - 7117, 2004-2006 (Box 72, Folder 45)
    Los Angeles Hotel Employees
  - 7308, 2001-2004 (Box 72, Folder 46)
    OSCO Drug
  - 7409, 2003-2006 (Box 72, Folder 47)
    Realty Advisory Board
  - 7411, 2002-2005 (Box 72, Folder 48)
    Bronx Realty Advisory Board
  - 7412, 2003-2006 (Box 72, Folder 49)
    Building and realty Institute
  - 7413, 2003-2006 (Box 72, Folder 50)
    BOMA
- Private agreements: Code nos.K5960-K6002 (Box 73)
  - 5760, 1992-1998 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    8/15/1992 - 8/15/1998
  - 5763, 1989-1998 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    8/1989 - 8/1998
  - 5766 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    See K#5763
  - 5767 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    See #k 5763
  - 5773, 1980-1995 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    8/1980 - 8/1995
  - 5783, 1980-1995 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - 5789, 1972-1991 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    11/1972 - 11/1991
  - 5791, 1988-2000 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    11/23/1988 - 11/4/2000
  - 5794, 1988-2003 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    6/5/1988 - 6/2003
  - 5801, 1990-1999 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    11/1990 - 11/1999